mamasmiles.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy ~ Mama Smiles

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or web site address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously via a private browser window.

Like most sites, we use Google Analytics to figure out which content is most useful to readers, as well as to find out how you discover this site (from social media, a web search, or through another site on the internet). Google Analytics reports where people who visit this site come from (down to a town level, which type of device or operating system they are using, and which type of browser. None of this information can be used to identify you.

Google does record visitor’s IP addresses. However, we don’t have access to this information. Google modifies it so that you cannot be identified specifically; only the area you live in.

**What do we use your information for?**

We use this information:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**Subscriber Newsletter**

If you choose to join my newsletter [via this sign up form](http://eepurl.com/ge2rRL), then your email address is required so that you can be sent the emails.

This data is collected and passed on to our email service provider, [Mailchimp](https://mailchimp.com/).

You may unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email. You can also email mamasmilesblog at gmail dot com and ask to be removed. Please make sure that you are using the same email address as you receive the emails from to do this.

The email service provider tracks which pages you visit and actions you take within the emails so that we can improve our email service.

We send 1 email a week and with our tracking try to make these as relevant to you as possible. Occasionally, we may include promotions for products.

We do not share your details with third parties.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [web site privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 4/25/2018

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

mamasmilesblog at gmail dot com
